(Penny:)to spend your birthday
in a bathroom,
(Penny:)I'm happy to do it with you.
(Sheldon:)Well, everyone will
think I'm weird.
(Penny:)Sweetie, you are weird.
(Penny:)Everyone knows you're weird,
(Penny:)but they're all still here
(Penny:)because they care
about you so much.
(Penny:)(knocking)
KRIPKE:
Hello.
(Barry(knocking):)Some of us need
to check our hair
(Barry(knocking):)because we might have a shot
with Leonard's mother.
(Scene:)Leonard.
Hey.
(Leslie:)It's been a while.
(Leonard:)Leslie.
(Leonard:)I can't remember
the last time we talked.
(Leonard:)So much has changed.
(Leslie:)Has it?
(Leonard:)Yeah, uh, um,
Penny and I got married.
(Leslie:)Wow, congratulations.
(Leslie:)You know, actually,
(Leslie:)I thought you'd be living
with Sheldon forever.
(Leonard:)Yeah, well...
(Leonard:)Don't be a stranger.